(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Square of Magic!
hololive 3rd Generation 5th Anniversary Live
Tamagotchi Nano Colorful × hololive Fantasy
ファンタジーぬいぐるみセット
Fantasy Plushie Sets
ホロライブファンタじっち
hololive 3rd Generation ver.
Hololive Fantas-gotchi
クリアブラック＆ラメのきらめく限定カラー
Clear Black & Lamé Sparkling Limited Color
3rd Generation
5th Anniversary
USADA PEKORA
兎田ぺこら
SHIRANUI FLARE
不知火フレア
SHIROGANE NOEL
白銀ノエル
HOUSHOU MARINE
宝鐘マリン
Square of Magic!
hololive 3rd Generation 5th Anniversary Live
#3期生5周年LIVE
#3rdGen5thAnniversaryLIVE
H-O-L-O-L-I-V-E
F-A-N-T-A-S-Y
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, start the challenge! Now!
REALITY FANTASY
作詞・作曲・編曲：山崎真吾 (SUPA LOVE)
Lyrics/Composition/Arrangement: Shingo Yamazaki (SUPA LOVE)
お宝探しに 大海原いざ出航だ
Searching for treasure, setting sail into the vast ocean now!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, start the challenge! Now!
今ここからもぴょんぴょん ワクワク ジャンプ ぴょんぴょん
From here on too, hop, hop, excited, jump, hop, hop!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, start the challenge! Now!
水平線 向こう側 新天地待っててね
Across the horizon, wait for me in the new world!
運命なんか飛び越してその先へ
Leaping past fate and heading beyond that!
さあ Reality Fantasy 二つの狭間へ
Now, to the space between Reality and Fantasy,
夢歌え 声高く一緒に
sing of dreams, our voices high together.
さあ まだ見ぬ世界へと 君を連れていくよ
Now, to the world yet unseen, I'll take you there,
みんなが繋がる物語
in the story that connects us all.
さあ 始まるよ
Now, it's starting!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, start the challenge! Now!
みんなの志 抱き挑む 騎士団集合
Embracing everyone's ambitions, Knight Order, assemble!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, start the challenge! Now!
胸に宿る太陽 風を切って さらに輝け
The sun dwelling in my chest, cutting through the wind, shine even brighter!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, start the challenge! Now!
迷いと夢 背負い 掲げたら 突撃だ
Carrying doubts and dreams, once held high, it's a charge!
妖精たち この旅 見守って
Fairies, please watch over this journey.
さあ Reality Fantasy 二つの狭間へ
Now, to the space between Reality and Fantasy,
帆をあげて 向かえユートピアへ
raise the sails, heading towards Utopia.
さあ それぞれの世界から 垣根を超えたら
Now, from each of our worlds, once we cross the barriers,
みんなが繋がる物語
in the story that connects us all.
さあ 始まるよ
Now, it's starting!
明るく陽気に荒波乗り越え ホーロー ライブ！
Cheerfully and brightly, overcoming rough waves, Hololive!
愛嬌開放 うさ耳澄まして ホーロー ライブ！
Unleashing charm, rabbit ears alert, Hololive!
騎士道と誇り 胸に刻んだら ホーロー ライブ！
With chivalry and pride etched in my heart, Hololive!
神話に伝わる 神秘な囁き ホーロー ライブ！
Mystical whispers passed down in myths, Hololive!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now, start the challenge! Now!
さあ Reality Fantasy 二つの狭間へ
Now, to the space between Reality and Fantasy,
夢歌え 声高く一緒に
sing of dreams, our voices high together.
さあ まだ見ぬ世界へと 君を連れていくよ
Now, to the world yet unseen, I'll take you there,
準備はほら できたよ ずっと先待ってたよ
look, we're ready, we've been waiting for a long time,
みんなが繋がる物語
in the story that connects us all.
さあ 始まるよ
Now, it's starting!
はい、始まりましたー！
Alright, here we go!
ホロライブ 3rd ジェネレーション フィフス アニバーサリー ライブ スクエア オブ マジック！
Hololive 3rd Generation 5th Anniversary Live: Square of Magic!
ハッシュタグは #3期生5周年LIVE になりますので、ぜひつけてたくさんポストしてください！
The hashtag is #3期生5周年LIVE, so please use it and post a lot!
ということで、一応、一旦自己紹介していきましょうか。ぺこちゃん。
So, let's start with a round of introductions. Peko-chan.
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Kon-peko, kon-peko, kon-peko!
5周年目になり、新たなうさぎになった、ホロライブ3期生の兎田ぺこらー！
Entering my 5th year and becoming a new rabbit, I'm Hololive 3rd Gen's Usada Pekora!
と。
...And.
と。とって感じ。いけいけ。
"And." That's how it is. Go, go!
こんぬーい！
Kon-nui!
ホロライブ3期生のハーフエルフ、えー、新たなハーフエルフとなった、不知火フレアです。よろしくお願いします。
The half-elf of Hololive 3rd Gen, well, having become a new half-elf, I'm Shiranui Flare. Nice to meet you.
そして、アイム、マッスルマッスル。と思いきや、優雅な、えーと...
And next, I'm... Muscle, muscle! Or so you'd think, but I'm an elegant, uh...
5周年で優雅になった、脳筋ではない、魔法も使っちゃう、白銀ノエルかもしれないのと。
having become elegant for our 5th year, I'm not a muscle brain, but maybe Shirogane Noel, who even uses magic... and.
何？何だって？
What? What did you say?
アホイ！えー、ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長のー...
Ahoy! Well, Hololive 3rd Gen, Captain of the Houshou Pirates...
んーと、何だ、5年目になったけど、一切老けない宝鐘マリンです！
Umm, it's my 5th year, but I'm Houshou Marine, who hasn't aged a bit!
せーの！
One, two!
我ら、ホロライブファンタジー！
We are, Hololive Fantasy!
はい！
Yes!
ということでね、えー...
So then, uh...
今回「Square of Magic!」ということで、ステージも映像に囲まれた空間でね、やらせていただいております。
This time it's "Square of Magic!", so we're performing in a space surrounded by visuals.
おおー！すごーい！
Ohhh! Amazing!
すごくて。このステージすごいね、今回演出がね、
It's incredible. This stage is amazing, the production this time around...
Square of Magic!
hololive 3rd Generation 5th Anniversary Live
かなり凝ってるので、ぜひ楽しみにしていてほしいです。
...is quite elaborate, so please look forward to it.
お願いしまーす。
Please do!
はい、いっぱい見てください。
Yes, please watch a lot.
でも、もうね、5周年ってことで。マジ早くない？5、5年？
But, you know, it's the 5th anniversary. Isn't that crazy fast? Five, five years?
早い。あっという間だね。
Fast. It went by in a flash.
5年も一緒にい るってことぺこらもんね。
It means we've been together for 5 years, right-peko?
じゃあ5年ちょっとやってきて、こう振り返ってみます？ぺこらちゃんどうぞ。
So, having done this for a bit over 5 years, shall we look back? Pekora-chan, go ahead.
そうですね。
Let's see.
ああ、そういう。長かったようで、
Ah, like that. It felt long,
あ、ポエム始まった。ポエムだ。
Ah, the poem started. It's a poem.
短かったようで。
and yet short.
配信前にやれよ、それ！
Do that before the stream!
いやでも、今ライブ始まって、今5周年で、今ここら辺でフワ～っときて。
But, the live has started, it's the 5th anniversary, and right around here, it's starting to feel real.
ああ、そうそう。
Ah, yeah, yeah.
はい。三期生でよかったなって思う、5年目。
Yes. I'm glad to be in the 3rd generation, in our 5th year.
6年目もよろぺこな～！
And please support us in our 6th year too-peko~!
はい、以上でーす！よろぺこ～！
Yes, that's all! Yoro-peko~!
じゃあフレアちゃん。
Now, Flare-chan.
はい。長かったようで、
Yes. It felt long,
あれ？被せた？
Wait, did you copy her?
でも、あっという間だった、フレアポエム。3期生の絆、
and yet, it went by in a flash. Flare's poem. The bond of the 3rd generation...
これからも、あるよね。
...it'll continue, right?
押忍。
Osu.
そして。はい。ああ、そうだね。
And... Yes. Ah, that's right.
5年と言ったら小学生が1年生から5年生になるという、そういう中途半端な感じです。
Speaking of 5 years, it's the time it takes for an elementary schooler to go from 1st to 5th grade. It's kind of a halfway point like that.
来年6年生じゃん。
They'll be in 6th grade next year.
でも、あと来年6年、頑張るぞという気持ち、あるよね。
But, the feeling of wanting to work hard next year, for our 6th year... we have it, right?
マリンは？
What about Marine?
3期生5年か。長かったようで、
3rd generation, 5 years. It felt long,
やばい、やばい。
Oh no, oh no.
短かった5年間。ぺこらちゃん、結婚したよね。
and yet short, these 5 years. Pekora-chan, we got married, didn't we?
え？
Eh?
結婚したこともありました。私達は結婚し、
There was a time we got married. We got married, and then...
そしてフレアちゃん。結婚したよね。
...Flare-chan, we got married too, didn't we?
え？え？
Eh? Eh?
したこともありました。え？
There was a time. Eh?
ノエルとも子作りしたね、そういえば。
I also made a child with Noel, come to think of it.
子作り？確かに父だ。
Made a child? True, I'm the father.
って感じで、いろいろありましたが、みんな仲良くやっていこう。
In that way, many things happened, but let's all keep getting along.
ということで、我々三期生、6年目も頑張っていきますので、
So, we in the 3rd generation will keep working hard in our 6th year too,
引き続き応援よろしくね！
so please continue to support us!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Please do!
さあ、まだまだライブはもうこれからですよ。もうこんな、駄弁ってる場合じゃない。
Now, the live is just getting started. This is no time to be chatting like this.
確かに。
True.
はい。もう楽しみにしてると思うので、もう次いっちゃいましょう、それでは。
Yes. Since I'm sure you're all looking forward to it, let's move on to the next one.
準備してきたいと思いまーす。
We'll go get ready.
じゃあ準備するので、一旦はけましょうか。
Then, since we need to prepare, shall we head backstage for a moment?
確かに。ああ、出てきた。扉だ。やったー！
True. Oh, it appeared. The door. Yay!
お城だ。すごい。どっこいしょーい！
It's a castle! Amazing! Heave-ho!
Chu chu yeah!
青空のラプソディ
作詞 林 英樹 / 作曲 佐藤純一
Blue Sky Rhapsody
Lyrics: Hideki Hayashi / Composition: Junichi Sato
ああ!なんてことだ 些細な過ちだ
Ah! What a thing. It's a trivial mistake.
自分のことになら さらさらっと解決
If it's about myself, I solve it in a flash.
どうして 突然逃げ切ったあとででしょう
Why is it that after suddenly making a getaway,
だけどなんだか いまさら元通り
but somehow, now it's back to how it was.
そんな気分になっちゃって
I've ended up in that kind of mood.
始まりはそんな風で
It starts off in that way,
つまりはらしくないようで
which means it's seemingly unlike me.
でも今じゃ 扉開けてほら
But now, open the door, look,
声が聞こえるよ さあ!
I can hear a voice. Now!
行こう! どこへでも
Let's go! Anywhere.
僕は君の翼に
I'll be your wings.
なれる勇気があるよ
I have the courage to become them.
(Please stay with me) どんな試練も
(Please stay with me) Any trial,
怖くない
is not scary,
その魔法があるから
because I have that magic.
(なんちゃって) 初めて出会う世界に
(Just kidding) To the world I encounter for the first time,
花束を贈ろう
let's offer a bouquet.
(Please make me happy) 今この瞬間
(Please make me happy) Right this moment,
結ばれるよ
we'll be tied together.
ちぐはぐなコミュニケーション
Our mismatched communication,
でも別に構わない
but it doesn't really matter.
明日から平和なら
If it's peaceful from tomorrow.
(Ah! どうしてまた)
(Ah! Why again?)
素直になれなくて
Can't I be honest?
自分のことで
With my own things,
(チュルッチュルッチュ) 傷つく
(Churu-churu-chu) getting hurt.
ギアはそのままで
Leave the gears as they are,
スピード上げていこう
and let's speed up.
だけどなんだか
But somehow,
兎田ぺこら / Usada Pekora
Usada Pekora / Usada Pekora
独りもどかしく
being alone is frustrating.
いつか思い出して
Someday, remember,
独りで泣いてもいいじゃない
that it's okay to cry alone.
誰にも頼らなくてもいい
You don't have to rely on anyone.
でも扉の向こう
But on the other side of the door,
騒がしい
it's noisy.
声が聞きたいよ 今
I want to hear your voice, now.
行こう! どこへでも
Let's go! Anywhere.
僕は君を背中に
I'll carry you on my back,
乗せて空を舞うよ
and dance through the sky.
(Please stay with me) たとえ心が
(Please stay with me) Even if our hearts,
離れても
are apart,
その時は笑ってて
keep smiling then.
(なんちゃって) 魔法みたいなこの世界に
(Just kidding) To this magic-like world,
青空のラプソディ
Blue Sky Rhapsody.
(Please make me happy) いついつまでも
(Please make me happy) Forever and ever,
奏でさせてよ
let me play it.
でこぼこなコンビネーション
Our bumpy combination,
でも別に構わない
but it doesn't really matter.
大丈夫さ　アッという間　平気まだ
It's okay, it'll be over in a blink, I'm still fine
ほんの小さな傷を
Even just a tiny scratch...
太陽にさらして
expose it to the sun
分け合ったよ　君と
and I shared it with you.
痛みは暑さの中に溶けていく
The pain melts away into the heat.
Chu chu yeah!
息切らし　弾ける僕ら
Out of breath, we're bursting forth,
手を叩いて
clapping our hands.
Chu chu yeah!
ドキドキ　リズムで反射　びしゃに
Reflection in a heart-pounding rhythm, soaking wet,
飛び跳ねて
leaping up.
Chu chu yeah!
息切らし　弾ける僕ら
Out of breath, we're bursting forth,
手を叩いて
clapping our hands.
Chu chu yeah!
ドキドキ　リズムで反射
Reflection in a heart-pounding rhythm,
あー　いいな
Ah, it's so good.
Hey!
どこまでも
No matter how far,
僕は君の翼に　なれる勇気があるよ
I have the courage to become your wings.
Please stay!
どんな試練も　怖くない
No trial is scary,
その魔法があるから
because of that magic.
君と出会い　世界は
Meeting you, the world
鮮やかさに溢れた
overflowed with vividness.
Nice to meet you!
四苦八苦なコミュニケーションでも
Even with difficult communication,
別に構わない　明日が平気なら
it doesn't really matter as long as tomorrow is fine.
Chu chu yeah!
Please me!
息をらし　見た
Out of breath, I saw...
三・二・一
3, 2, 1
Without you!
晴る
Sunny
あなたは風のように
You are like the wind,
目を閉じては夕暮れ
closing your eyes at twilight.
何を思っているんだろうか
I wonder what you're thinking about.
瞼を開いていた
You were opening your eyelids,
あなたの目はビードロ
and your eyes are glass beads.
少しだけ春の匂いがした
There was just a slight scent of spring.
晴れに晴れ　花よ咲け
Sunny, sunny, let the flowers bloom,
咲いて晴るのせい
bloom because of the spring sun.
降り止まぬ雨でさえ
Even the rain that won't stop falling
あなたを飾り晴る
will adorn you and make it sunny.
胸を打つ音よ鳴れ
The sound that strikes my heart, ring out!
僕ら晴る風
We are the spring breeze.
あの雲も越えてゆけ
Go beyond those clouds, too,
遠くまで
as far as you can.
あなたは晴れのように
You are like the clear sky,
目を閉じては青色
closing your eyes to the blue.
何が悲しいのだろうか
I wonder what's so sad.
瞼を開いている
You are opening your eyelids,
あなたの目にビードロ
with glass beads in your eyes.
今少し雨の匂いがした
Just now, there was a slight scent of rain.
泣きに泣け　空よ泣け
Cry, cry, cry, oh sky,
泣いて雨のせい
cry because of the rain.
降りしきる雨でさえ
Even the pouring rain,
雲の上では晴れ
above the clouds, it's sunny.
土を打つ音よ鳴れ
The sound striking the earth, ring out!
僕ら晴る荒れ
We are the spring storm.
あの海も越えてゆく
Go beyond that sea, too,
遠くまで
as far as you can.
...遠くまで
...far away.
降り雨　草をなびかせ
Falling rain, making the grass sway.
羊雲　あれも春のせい
Altocumulus clouds, those too are because of spring.
風のよう　胸に春のせ
Like the wind, spring is in my heart.
春を待つ
Waiting for spring.
晴れに晴れ　空よ咲け
Clearer than clear, oh sky, bloom.
裂いて春のせい
Ripping through, it's because of spring.
降り止めば　雨でさえ
If it stops falling, even the rain...
あなたを飾る春
...is spring that adorns you.
胸を打つ　音奏で
Playing the sound that strikes the heart.
僕ら春風
We are the spring breeze.
音に聞く　晴るの風
Listening to the sound, the clear spring breeze.
さあこの歌よ　凪げ！
Now, let this song be calm!
晴れに晴れ　花よ咲け
Clearer than clear, oh flowers, bloom.
咲いて春のせい
Blooming, it's because of spring.
あの雲も　越えて行け
Go beyond even those clouds.
遠くまだ　遠くまで
Farther yet, even farther away.
唯一無二のこの技で　荒らそう本邸
With this one-and-only technique, I'll raid the main residence.
禁忌、禁術、明らかなもって　反則次元、この世のものではないです
Taboos, forbidden arts, clearly a foul dimension, it's not of this world.
無理ゲー、それ聞いてないって　Ay、ライバル口を揃えて
Impossible game, I didn't hear about that, Ay, rivals all saying in unison...
Wow、ライバル口を揃えて　バグで、バグれ、認めねえぜって
Wow, rivals all saying in unison, "It's a bug, it's glitchy, I won't accept it."
マジで？これお前、生身で？
Seriously? You're doing this in the flesh?
生身のまま、生身のまま、イェー、イェー、イェー
Just as I am, in the flesh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born
実力を発揮し切る前に　相手の方がバックれてくらしい
Before I can show my true power, it seems my opponents run away.
上がり切るハードル、ベリーハッピー　明快に断トツ的に快
The hurdles keep rising, very happy, clearly and overwhelmingly pleasant.
相変わらず脱皮してる毎日　Bling, Bling, Bling
I'm shedding my skin every day as usual, Bling, Bling, Bling.
他の何の光もいらない、お前、アイソーリー、アイシーシー
I don't need any other light, you, I'm sorry, I see see.
パッと見、出来ない事ばかりだけど　ベリーハッピー、あ、キレてる、呆れてる周り
At first glance, it's all things I can't do, but very happy, ah, everyone's fed up.
恵まれてる家族、友達、ハッピー　もう反則的な立ち位置、俺に任しとけばいい
Blessed with family and friends, happy, already a foul position, just leave it to me.
教科書に無い、問題集に無い　超抜なマジな今
Not in textbooks, not in workbooks, a truly exceptional "now."
鏡よ鏡、答えちゃって　Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
Mirror, mirror, give me the answer: Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah.
生身のまま行ける処まで　To the next, to the 1番上
Going as far as I can in the flesh, to the next, to the very top.
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born
To the next, to the 1番上
To the next, to the very top.
Ey-day、俺のままで居るだけで超フレックス
Every day, just being myself is super flex.
Ey-day、誰も口を挟めない
Every day, no one can butt in.
Ey-day、俺のままで居るだけで超フレックス
Every day, just being myself is super flex.
Ey-day、誰も口を挟ませない
Every day, I won't let anyone butt in.
イェ、イェ、イェ、隠し切れない才能も余裕で、Bling, Bling
Yeah, yeah, yeah, even my undeniable talent is a breeze, Bling, Bling.
この存在自体が文化財のノリで、Bling, Bling
This existence itself is like a cultural asset, Bling, Bling.
後継者は居る、免許は無い、愛車は、Bling, Bling
I have successors, no license, my favorite car is Bling, Bling.
全国各地揺らすエピック、このベロが、Bling, Bling
An epic shaking the whole country, this tongue is Bling, Bling.
パレットなら満タン、変幻自在生身の言霊
Palette is full, phantasmagoric spiritual power of words in the flesh.
音楽、幸運、勝利の女神、今宵も三股、ブン、ブン、ブン
Music, luck, goddess of victory, triple-timing tonight too, vroom, vroom, vroom.
漫画みたいな奴らとまんまで、やり合ってしまってる漫画
Just like in a manga, fighting with guys like those in a manga.
圧倒的力、この頭と口から
Overwhelming power, from this head and mouth.
この身体タトゥーは入ってない、この面、傷も付いてない
This body has no tattoos, this face has no scars.
繰り返しやらかしてくダメージが、いかつい年輪を刻む皺
Repeated screw-ups become wrinkles that carve tough annual rings.
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang,
俺のまま Bling して Bang して Bang する為に降臨した日本
I descended on Japan to Bling, Bang, and Bang as myself.
鏡よ鏡、答えちゃって　Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah
Mirror, mirror, give me the answer: Who's the best? I'm the best! Oh yeah.
生身のまま行ける処まで　To the next, to the 1番上
Going as far as I can in the flesh, to the next, to the very top.
Bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang, bling-bang-bang-born
To the next, to the 1番上
To the next, to the very top.
Ey-day、俺のままで居るだけで超フレックス
Every day, just being myself is super flex.
Ey-day、誰も口を挟めない
Every day, no one can butt in.
Ey-day、俺のままで居るだけで超フレックス
Every day, just being myself is super flex.
Ey-day、誰も口を挟ませない
Every day, I won't let anyone butt in.
あざとみを足して
Adding a bit of calculated cuteness...
ふふ、後ろ姿みたいで笑えば...
Hehe, laughing at how I look from behind...
夜にも美し怪物...
A monster beautiful even in the night...
女の子で出来上がり
Finished off as a girl.
眉も目も唇も
Brows, eyes, and lips too,
好きなように描き足しな
draw them in as you like.
厚い眼差し重ねなきゃ
Unless you layer on a thick gaze,
千年恋も冷めちゃうわ
even a thousand-year love will go cold.
運命なんて生まれた日より選んだ時決まるもの
Fate is decided not by birth, but by choice.
今も今もひっくるめ今をきっとちゃんと愛してね
Include everything, and please love me as I am now.
正面で見ても横から見ても下から見てもいい女って
From the front, the side, or from below, a beauty...
困っちゃう... (困っちゃう...)
it's trouble... (it's trouble...)
君は全方向美少女
You're an all-direction beauty.
ね、困っちゃう... (困っちゃう...)
Hey, it's trouble... (it's trouble...)
中身外見も全部愛して受け取るよ
I'll love and accept you, inside and out.
Eyes on you every time I find out you're sweet
Eyes on you every time I find out you're much more sweet
アイラインを跳ね上げ
Winged eyeliner flicked up,
天まで届くまつ毛
eyelashes reaching for the sky,
頬にバラ咲かせてルージュで嘘を色付けて
roses blooming on cheeks, coloring lies with rouge.
よく人に好かれんな
People often like me,
見せ方も分かってます
I know how to show myself off.
美しさも愛嬌も全能力を与えます
I give my all to beauty and charm.
幸福なんて一生をかけてそっとずっと集めるもの
Happiness is gathered gently over a lifetime.
今も今も味わって今をきっとちゃんと愛してね
Savor every moment, and please love me as I am now.
正面で見ても横から見ても下から見てもいい女って
From the front, the side, or from below, a beauty...
困っちゃう... (困っちゃう...)
it's trouble... (it's trouble...)
君は全方向美少女
You're an all-direction beauty.
ね、困っちゃう... (困っちゃう...)
Hey, it's trouble... (it's trouble...)
中身外見も全部愛して受け取って
Love and accept me, inside and out.
Eyes on you every time I find out you're much more sweet
I find you're much more much more sweet
君は全方向美少女
You're an all-direction beauty.
そろり、そろり、いい女はどこかな～？
Gently, gently... where is the beauty?~
はーい、横から見て、下から見て、上から見て...
Right here! Look from the side, below, and above...
あれ、忍者じゃない？ちょっと待ってよ
Wait, aren't you a ninja? Hold on a second.
船長！さっき歌ってた人と違うぺこ！めっちゃいい女だと思ったら、なんか喋ってみたら違ったみたいな...
Captain! You're different from the person singing just now-peko! I thought you were a real beauty, but you're different once you talk...
ということでね、皆さん、この3期生ライブいかがですか？3期生ライブとか言って、まぁ3期生ライブか、いかがですか？無理やりｗ
And with that, everyone, how are you enjoying this 3rd Gen Live? Calling it a 3rd Gen Live, well it is one, but how is it? I'm forcing it lol.
こちらね、マリンが結構ね、割と全体の曲とか演出とか考えたんですけど...
For this, I, Marine, thought about the overall setlist and staging...
ありがとうね、天才、最高！
Thank you! You're a genius, the best!
ね、このソロ曲なんだけど、でもなんかソロなんだけど、
Right, about this solo song, even though it's a solo,
やっぱ3期生全員いる感じは出したくて。
I really wanted to give the feeling of all 3rd Gen being there.
全体的に3期生が常にどっかしら映り込むような感じになるように、そここだわってやりました！
I focused on making sure the 3rd Gen members were always appearing somewhere throughout!
天才！天才です！ありがとう！いい女！
Genius! You're a genius! Thank you! Beauty!
あ、よ、よいしょ、下から見て！あ、ちょっと違うかも。もう一回、見てくれてる、見てくれてるよ！
Ah, yo-heave-ho, look from below! Ah, maybe that's a bit off. One more time, they're watching, they're watching!
よっ！よっ！ありがとう！みんなありがとう！
Yo! Yo! Thank you! Thank you everyone!
よっとなんか、フルコンボだドンみたいなノリがすごいよｗ
Whoa, that 'Full Combo!' energy is incredible lol.
はい、そんな感じでね、ちょっと、なんか結構みんなにも合う曲、かつ演出も楽しい感じで考えたので、
Yeah, so I picked songs that suit everyone and thought of fun staging, so...
この後もね、全部そういう感じで、どっかしらに、そう、みんな3期生を入れつつ...
Everything from here on will be like that, with 3rd Gen members popping in somewhere...
曲がみんなの声に合っていつつ、
The songs will match everyone's voices,
演出が楽しい感じになるように、こだわって作られているので楽しみに見てください！
and with fun staging. They were made with care, so please look forward to them!
楽しんでいってねー！ということでね、ここからはデュエット曲になります！
Have fun! And with that, from here on we'll have duet songs!
え、待って、誰と誰？誰と誰？誰と誰？
Wait, who's with who? Who's with who? Who's with who?
マリンと組みたい人！マリンと組も！マリンと組も！
Anyone who wants to pair with Marine! Let's pair with Marine! Let's pair with Marine!
ズルい、ズルい、歌いたい、歌いたい、歌いたい...
No fair, no fair! I want to sing, I want to sing, I want to sing...
だから、これ、これでいいじゃない、これで。これでいいじゃない、いいじゃない、ということでね...
So, this, this is fine, right? This. This is good, it's good. And so...
はい、誰と誰がどんな歌を歌うのか、また他のメンバーが現れることはあるのか。
Yes, who will sing what song, and will other members appear?
お楽しみにしていってください！
Please look forward to it!
フレアちゃん、一緒に歌ってくれるんだもんね。
Flare-chan, you're singing with me, right?
じゃないと一緒に歌おうね。歌おうな。イエーイ！
Of course, let's sing together. Let's do it. Yay!
じゃあ、みんな、立ち位置について。もたもたしないで。
Okay, everyone, get to your positions. Don't dawdle.
はい、立ち位置について。お局さんｗ はい、いいわね。
Yes, get in position. You're acting like a boss lady lol. Yes, that's good.
君を泣かすから だから一緒にはいれないな
I'll make you cry, so I can't stay with you.
君を泣かすから 早く忘れてほしいんだ
I'll make you cry, so I want you to forget me quickly.
人間だからね たまには違うものも食べたいね
I'm only human, I want to eat something different sometimes.
君を泣かすから そう君を泣かすから
Because I'll make you cry, yes, I'll make you cry.
でも味気ないないないんだよね
But it's so tasteless, isn't it?
会いたいたくないんだよね
I don't want to meet you, do I?
君以外会いたくないんだよね
I don't want to meet anyone but you, do I?
なんて勝手だね
How selfish of me.
大体曖昧なんだよね
It's mostly vague, isn't it?
愛の存在証明なんて
Things like proof of love's existence.
君が教えてくれないか
Won't you tell me about it?
何十回の夜を過ごしたって得られぬような
The kind you couldn't get even if you spent dozens of nights,
愛してるを並べてみて
Try lining up "I love you"s.
何十回の夜を過ごしたって得られぬような
The kind you couldn't get even if you spent dozens of nights,
最高級のフルコースを頂戴
Give me the finest full-course meal.
君を泣かすから きっと一生は無理だよね
Because I'll make you cry, a whole lifetime is probably impossible, right?
君を泣かすから 胸がとても痛いんだ
Because I'll make you cry, my chest hurts so much.
人間だからね たまには分かり合えなくなって
Since we're human, sometimes we just stop understanding each other.
君を泣かすから
Because I'll make you cry,
また君を泣かすから
I'll make you cry again.
でも自信がないないないないんだよね
But I have no-no-no-no confidence, you know?
変わりたくないないないないんだよね
I don't want to change-change-change-change, you know?
君以外会いたくないんだよね
I don't want to see anyone but you, you know?
なんで勝手だね
How selfish of me.
大体曖昧だったよね
It was mostly vague, wasn't it?
愛の存在証なんて
Things like proof of love's existence.
君がそこにいるのにね
Even though you're right there.
何百回の夜を過ごしたって得られぬような
The kind you couldn't get even if you spent hundreds of nights,
愛してるを並べてみて
Try lining up "I love you"s.
何百回の夜を過ごしたって得られぬような
The kind you couldn't get even if you spent hundreds of nights,
最高級のフルコースを頂戴
Give me the finest full-course meal.
離れないで傍に居てくれたのは
The one who stayed by my side without leaving,
結局君一人だったよね
Was you alone in the end, wasn't it?
涙のスパイスは君の胸に
The spice of tears will likely remain,
残ってしまうだろうけど
In your heart, but...
何千回の夜を過ごしたって得られぬような
The kind you couldn't get even if you spent thousands of nights,
愛してるを並べるから
Because I'll line up "I love you"s.
何千回の夜を過ごしたって得られぬような
The kind you couldn't get even if you spent thousands of nights,
最高級のフルコースを頂戴
Give me the finest full-course meal.
何万回の夜を過ごしたって忘れぬような
The kind you won't forget even if you spend tens of thousands of nights,
愛してるを並べるから
Because I'll line up "I love you"s.
何万回の夜を過ごしたって忘れぬような
The kind you won't forget even if you spend tens of thousands of nights,
最高級のフルコースを頂戴
Give me the finest full-course meal.
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
作詞：森雪之丞 作曲：清岡千穂
Lyrics: Yukinojo Mori / Composition: Chiho Kiyooka
光る雲を突き抜け Fly Away
Piercing through the glowing clouds, fly away
(Fly Away)
からだじゅうに広がるパノラマ
A panorama spreading throughout my body
顔を蹴られた地球が怒って
The Earth is angry from being kicked in the face,
(怒って)
(It's angry)
火山を爆発させる
Making volcanoes erupt
溶けた氷の中に
Inside the melted ice,
恐竜がいたら 玉乗り仕込みたいね
If there's a dinosaur, I want to teach it how to balance on a ball
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA 何が起きても気分は
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA, no matter what happens, I feel like...
へのへのカッパ
It's a piece of cake
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA 胸がパチパチするほど騒ぐ元気玉
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA, a Spirit Bomb making my chest crackle with energy
Sparking!
空を急降下ジェットコースター
Diving through the sky on a roller coaster
(コースター)
(Coaster)
落ちてゆくよ パニックの手前
Falling down, just on the verge of panic
突き抜け Fly Away
Fly away, piercing through!
広がるパノラマ
The panorama spreads out!
顔を蹴られた地球が怒って
The Earth, having been kicked in the face, gets angry
火山を爆発させる
And makes its volcanoes explode!
悩む時間はないよ
There's no time to worry!
どこかに潜む「びっくり」に会いたいから
Because I want to meet the "surprise" hiding somewhere!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
頭からっぽの方が
It's better to have an empty head
夢詰め込める
So you can stuff it with dreams!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
笑顔ウルトラゼットで
With a smile that's Ultra Z
今日もアイ・アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ
Today too, ai-ai-ai-ai-ai!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きても気分は
No matter what happens, I feel like
へのへのカッパ
It's a piece of cake!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど
So much that my chest crackles
騒ぐ元気玉...
The Genki-Dama goes wild...
Sparking!
ちゅ、多様性。
作詞：あの / 真部脩一　作曲：真部脩一
Chu, Tayousei.
Lyrics: Ano / Shuichi Mabe  Composition: Shuichi Mabe
我愛你　酔いが醒めない
I love you, I can't sober up
我愛你　恋が醒めない
I love you, this love won't fade
我愛你　様々の成れの果て
I love you, the result of various things
嗚呼して
Do it like that
無問題　頬を摩ってみたい
No problem, I want to try rubbing cheeks
トラウマの味も反対
The taste of trauma is also opposite
お手々繋いでハイ、ポーズ
Hold hands and say, "Cheese!"
余韻
Afterglow
喉の奥がチクンチクン
The back of my throat prickles
僕は毒ムドクンムドクン
I'm poison, thumping away
孤独な鼓動 消してみてよ
Try making this lonely heartbeat disappear
愛も恋もドッカイして
Toss aside both love and romance
僕を独占して
Keep me all to yourself
このまま中毒になるまで
Until I become addicted just like this
チュしよう
Let's kiss
ゲゲゲロ　ゲゲゲロ　ゲロチュー
Get-get-puke, get-get-puke, puke-kiss
熱く蕩けるくらいに 溢れた気持ちが
These overflowing feelings are melting hot
たまらないでしょ
It's irresistible, right?
ゲゲゲロ　ゲゲゲロ　ゲロチュー
Get-get-puke, get-get-puke, puke-kiss
ゲロゲロ 我愛你 無問題
Puke-puke, I love you, no problem
ゲゲゲロチュー
Get-get-puke-kiss
どんちゃん 勝負はいつもどんちゃん
Rowdy, the showdown is always rowdy
僕にいわせりゃちんぷんかん
If you ask me, it's all Greek
踏み出した一歩はロンでしょう
That first step you took is a "Ron," isn't it?
もう何回 やられればいい
How many more times must I be beaten?
終わんない 忘れられない
It won't end, I can't forget
終わんない レトロときめき変容
It won't end, a retro transformation of heart-throbs
余韻
Afterglow
喉の奥がチクンチクン
The back of my throat prickles
僕は毒ムドクンムドクン
I'm poison, thumping away
心底丸ごと 引き摺り出してみてよ
Try dragging it all out from the bottom of my heart
気持ちいいね 面倒くさいけど
It feels good, though it's a bother
やっぱ照れくさいけど
Though it's embarrassing after all
死ぬまで忘れられない
I won't forget until the day I die
チュしよう
Let's kiss
狂った街はゾンビであふれる
The crazy city is overflowing with zombies
君は僕に恋してる
You're in love with me
溶ける胸に繋がるロープを引いたよ
I pulled the rope connected to my melting heart
行くよ ゲゲゲロ ゲゲゲロ ゲロチュー
Here I go! Get-get-puke, get-get-puke, puke-kiss
ゲゲゲロ ゲゲゲロ ゲロチュー
Get-get-puke, get-get-puke, puke-kiss
マジで狂えるくらいの 現しさが
This reality that could drive me truly mad
美しいでしょ
Is beautiful, right?
ゲゲゲロ ゲゲゲロ ゲロチュー
Get-get-puke, get-get-puke, puke-kiss
せーの どんちゃん 終わんない
One, two! Rowdy, it won't end
ゲゲゲロチュー
Get-get-puke-kiss
ほらね 我愛你 無問題
See? I love you, no problem
ゲゲゲロチュー
Get-get-puke-kiss
アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ　今日はボレロ
Ai-ai-ai-ai, today is a Bolero
蕩けちゃいそうね
It feels like I'm melting
甘酸っぱいレモン　Q, my 人生
Sweet and sour lemon, Q, my life
いっぱい万杯
Full to the brim
オーブン、足してはモリモリ
Adding more to the oven, high as can be
おかわりはアンコールしたいね
I want to encore for seconds!
愛包ダンスホール
作詞：Gohgo　作曲：涼木シンジ & Gohgo
Aipai Dance Hall
Lyrics: Gohgo  Composition: Shinji Suzaki & Gohgo
終わらない愛包ダンスホール
The unending Aipai Dance Hall
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
3.1415926535のパイだって
Even with pi being 3.1415926535
割り切れない気持ち抱えてるよ
I'm holding onto feelings that don't add up
ロボ人も原人もエンジんも 円陣組んで仲良くやれたらとか
Robots, cavemen, engines, if only we could all huddle up and get along
割り切れない命 戦いのヘヴン
An indivisible life, a battle heaven
今宵はいいんじゃない？ ほら O-E-O-E-O-E-O-E-O
Isn't tonight just fine? Look, O-E-O-E-O-E-O-E-O
踊ればいいんじゃない？ ほら ふりふりふりなれば
Why not just dance? Look, just shake shake shake
牛設状態 涙腺画線が厳選をせ
Crowded state, tear ducts line up and select
遊ばなだらかんだ サンサラ
If you don't play, you're just drifting, samsara
何言ってんだ？
What are you even saying?
高まった感度の再会
A reunion of heightened sensitivity
集まった愛情のワイバイ
A gathering of affection, bye-bye
間違った上等の忍耐 愛せるが重なって
Mistaken, superior patience, love overlaps
振る舞った人類の状態
The state of humanity's behavior
熱いミートパイみたいだね！
It's like a hot meat pie, isn't it!
パ・パ・パ・パ・パ・パ・パイ！ PAI!
Pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi! PIE!
アイパイアイパイでほらほらよ
Eye-pie, eye-pie, look look
トロケテショーン甘酸っぱレモン 9は人類いっぱい満杯大
Melting, sweet and sour lemon, 9 is humanity full to the brim
カンパイ完全にほらほらよ
Cheers, completely, look look
耳フィーユみたいね愛一人 頭の中パパパパパパパイ
Like a mille-feuille, love for one, inside my head pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi
生やかな野だなノリの上連
A fresh field, regular on the rhythm
飲もうアイパイ imagine all the peopleの最低
Let's drink eye-pie, imagine all the people's lowest point
ダンスホールでイマジンの黄色
On the dance floor, the yellow of imagine
三杯今日はそれよ 交わって人類は重なってワケ
Three cups, that's it for today, mingling, humanity overlaps, that's why
おかわり欲しいでしょ？
You want a second helping, don't you?
全人類個性舞踏会
All humanity's individuality dance party
目指すべき一日は レンジでチンしてパイになるような
The day to aim for is one that turns into a pie in the microwave
脳味噌もトロトロの 要成就実現をスローガンに all night
With brains all gooey, with the slogan of fulfillment all night
踊り待って煩悩は淘汰 隙待って政治を誤差
Waiting to dance, worldly desires are weeded out, waiting for gaps, politics is an error
パ・パ・パ・パ・パ・パ・パイ！
Pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi!
人類最高のダンスタイム！
Humanity's greatest dance time!
アイパイダンスホール
Aipai Dancehall
あらら アイパイダンスホール
Oh my, Aipai Dancehall
アイパイダンスホール
Aipai Dancehall
僕らが生まれて初めて知る音は 心臓の鼓動だろう？
The first sound we know when we're born is probably our heartbeat, right?
ドッドンドッドン それはリズムと死体
Thump, thump, it's rhythm and a corpse
古も今どきも ハイブリッドが僕らを包み繋いでんだろう
From ancient times to now, a hybrid probably wraps us up and connects us
パ・パ・パ・パ・パ・パ・パイ！ PAI!
Pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi! PIE!
アイパイアイパイでほらほらよ
Eye-pie, eye-pie, look look
トロケテショーン甘酸っぱレモン 9は人類いっぱい満杯大
Melting, sweet and sour lemon, 9 is humanity full to the brim
カンパイ完全にほらほらよ
Cheers, completely, look look
耳フィーユみたいね愛一人 頭の中パパパパパパパイ
Like a mille-feuille, love for one, inside my head pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi-pi
ラララ...
La la la...
まるでバージンロードで踊ってるみたい 生まれ変わったような気分です
It's like dancing down the wedding aisle, I feel like I've been reborn
カンパイね今日はそれよ 交わって人類は重なって笑って
Cheers, that's it for today, mingling, humanity overlaps and laughs
テ・レ・テ・テ...
Te-re-te-te...
寂しいのまま終わりは近づくけどさ
The end approaches while it's still lonely
終わらないパイのように続けりゃいい
Should just keep it going like the never-ending pi
計算なんてできないが
Calculations are impossible but
アイパイアイパイ ダンスホール 今日はそれよ
Eye-pie, eye-pie, dancehall, today that's it
トロケテショーン甘酸っぱレモン 9は人類いっぱい満杯大
Melting, sweet and sour lemon, 9 is humanity full to the brim
また食べに来てね！
Come back and eat again!
あなたならいつでもいいよ おかわり欲しいでしょ？
If it's you, anytime is fine, you want a second helping, don't you?
アイパイダンスホール
Aipai Dancehall
おかわりなら欲しい...
If it's a second helping, I want it...
アイパイダンスホール
Aipai Dancehall
どうぞ！
Here you go!
マリンの横に...
Next to Marine...
どした？
What's up?
マリンちゃん転ばしちゃって...
You made Marine-chan fall over...
転ばしていきました！
I sent her tumbling!
ドーンと！
With a bang!
はい、あげました！
Yes, I gave her a lift!
ということで皆さん！
So anyway, everyone!
はい、デュエットどうでしたか？
How did you like the duet?
いい感じぺこだね！
It was great, peko!
最高だった！
It was the best!
最高だぜ！
It was awesome!
イエーイ！
Yeeeah!
なんかご雑な感じ...
That felt a bit messy...
エモいことにしなくちゃ。
We have to make it emotional.
エモかった、エモかったでしょ、もっと。
It was emotional, wasn't it, even more so.
エモかったよね、マリンとね。
It was emotional, right, Marine?
ね、オ・オ・オ・オ！
Right, Oh-oh-oh-oh!
エモかった！エモかった！エモかった！
It was emotional! It was emotional! It was emotional!
イエーイ！ということでね...
Yeeeah! So anyway...
適当ぺこじゃない？
Aren't you being a bit lazy, peko?
お前が一番適当だっただろ！
You were the laziest of all!
あ、そうか。
Ah, right.
いいじゃん、よかったじゃん。
It's fine, it was good.
はい、ということでね、告知タイムです！
Alright, it's time for some announcements!
イエーイ！告知！
Yeeeah! Announcements!
ドーン！
Ta-da!
ドーンと！
And ta-da!
あ、すごい、かわいい！
Oh, wow, so cute!
ということで、ホロライブ3期生5周年記念グッズが出ます！
So, Hololive 3rd generation 5th anniversary goods are coming out!
やったー！
Yaaaay!
さ、たくさんありますので、さくっと見ていきましょう！
There are a lot, so let's take a quick look!
じゃあまずフレア、紹介お願いします！
First, Flare, please introduce them!
はい！
Okay!
はい、一つ目は、『ステージジオラマアクリルスタンド』！
First is the 'Stage Diorama Acrylic Stand'!
Nardack先生に描き下ろしていただきました！
Illustrated by Nardack-sensei!
今回のライブをイメージしたステージ風の立体のジオラマアクリルスタンドです！
It's a 3D stage-style diorama acrylic stand based on this live!
4人分ちゃんとあるので、隣に合わせる、隣り合わせはもちろん...
There's one for each of the four, so you can put them side by side...
上に重ねることもできて、いろんな飾り方ができます！
Or stack them up! There are many ways to display them!
ぜひ4人分集めて飾ってください！
Please collect all four and display them!
次、ノエル！
Next, Noel!
はい！よしよしよし...
Yes! Alright, alright...
はい、二つ目は、『Square of Magic! 法被』！
Second is the 'Square of Magic! Happi' coat!
ハッピーハッピー！
Happy, happy!
ということで、どどんと大きくイラストが入ってるので、推しアピールにもってこいです！
It has a large illustration on it, so it's perfect for showing your support!
Square of Magic! 法被 (全4種)
イラスト: Nardack
サイズ: フリーサイズ
Square of Magic! Happi (All 4 types)
Illustration: Nardack
Size: One size fits all
え、4人それぞれ、ノエルの、
Wait, each of the four has one, including Noel's,
ですが、一部はね、お揃いになっているので、こちらはですね、
but some parts are matching, so these are...
えー、箱推しの人も、ぜひぜひ、ということで、
So for those who support the whole group, please check them out!
かっこいいー！
Cool!
静かにしろ！
Quiet down!
えー、かっこいいデザインなってるので、着るだけじゃなく、
It's a cool design, so it's not just for wearing,
飾っても最高なハッピとなってます！
but it's also a happi coat that looks great displayed!
ハッピーになりましょう！では次、ぺこら！
Let's be happy! Next, Pekora!
おーい、はーい、ぺこらだよー、はい次はこちら！
Hey, yes, it's Pekora. Next is this!
ランダムスクエア缶バッジ (全8種からランダムで1個封入)
イラスト: Nardack
サイズ: 約H58xW58mm
Random Square Pin Badges (1 random out of 8 types included)
Illustration: Nardack
Size: Approx. H58xW58mm
ランダムスクエア缶バッジ！
Random Square Pin Badges!
今回のね、ライブテーマに合わせた、スクエアの缶バッジでーす！
These are square pin badges that match the theme of this live!
えっとね、四角なので、並べやすく、
Well, since they're square, they're easy to line up,
イラストは、グッズ用ビジュアルと、立ち絵から、
and the illustrations include the goods visual and standing poses,
2種類ずつの、全8種類！ランダムでお届け！
two of each, for a total of eight types! Delivered at random!
イエーイ！
Yay!
次、マリン！
Next, Marine!
はい、って普通こういうの背の順じゃないの？
Yes... Wait, isn't it usually in order of height?
よいしょ、ちょっと、こけた！
Whoops... Wait, I fell!
大丈夫、こけてません、はい次はこちら！
I'm okay, I didn't fall. Next is this!
スクエアポケットトートバッグ
前面にクリアポケット付き
サイズ: 本体/約H34xW28xD10cm
Square Pocket Tote Bag
Clear pocket on the front
Size: Main body / Approx. H34xW28xD10cm
ちょ、グダグダですみません、これ頑張る！
Sorry for being a mess, I'll do my best!
落ち着いて、落ち着いて、はいこちら！
Calm down, calm down... Here it is!
スクエアポケットトートバッグです！
It's the Square Pocket Tote Bag!
これもですね、今回のライブをイメージして、
This one also features the live's image,
前面にロゴなどが入ったスクエア型のポケットがついています。
with a square pocket on the front including the logo and more.
A4が入る大きさになってるので、使い勝手抜群です！
It fits A4 size, so it's very practical!
はい、まだまだあるので紹介しちゃいますね。次はこちら！
Yes, there's still more to show. Next is this!
スクエアイヤーカフ (全4種)
サイズ: 約H14xW10xD12mm
Square Ear Cuffs (All 4 types)
Size: Approx. H14xW10xD12mm
はい、スクエアイヤーカフです！さりげなく、推しアピールがしたい方に、
Yes, it's the Square Ear Cuffs! For those who want to subtly show off their favorite,
おすすめ。
these are recommended.
それぞれの名前や誕生日が入っているので、
They have each member's name and birthday on them,
片耳ずつ、別のものを付けてもいいし、両方付けてもいいし、
so you can wear a different one on each ear, or wear both,
使い方は自由です。
it's up to you.
実はね、キービジュアルで、船長たちも付けているので、
Actually, we're wearing them in the key visual,
お揃いにしちゃってください。
so please get them to match with us.
マリンパパ？なんかすごい…
Marine Papa? It's like...
すごい力持ってる。アシュラ！
he has incredible power. Asura!
そして最後はこちら！
And finally, this!
ブロマイドケース
3期生からの複製メッセージ入り!
イラスト: Nardack
Bromide Case
Includes reproduction messages from the 3rd generation!
Illustration: Nardack
ブロマイドケース！こちら、なんと！
The Bromide Case! And for this, believe it or not!
ご購入いただいた方には、キービジュアルのブロマイドと、
Purchasers will receive a bromide of the key visual and
我々4人の手書きメッセージが書かれたメッセージも付いてきます、
a message with handwritten messages from the four of us...
ちょ、待って間違えた。
Wait, I messed up.
手書きメッセージが書かれたカードも付いてきます！
A card with handwritten messages will also be included!
カード！
A card!
はい、メッセージの内容は届いてからのお楽しみです。
Yes, you'll have to wait until it arrives to see the message content.
こちらのね、メッセージは複製なので、ご了承下さい。以上です！
Please note that the messages are reproductions. That's all!
はい、今回はフルセット販売はないので、
Yes, there's no full set sale this time,
欲しいものをそれぞれ単品購入していただく形になります。
so you'll need to buy each item individually.
数量限定もないので、皆さん、よく吟味して選んでくださいね！
There's no quantity limit either, so everyone, please take your time and choose carefully!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
はい、ということで盛りだくさんなグッズ紹介でした。
Yes, that was a lot of merchandise.
詳細は、グッズ販売ページなどから、ご確認下さい。
Please check the sales page for details.
では告知も終わったところで、ライブも終盤に入っております。
Now that the announcements are over, the live is entering its final stages.
改めて、今までの5周年と、
Once again, reflecting on the 5th anniversary so far,
今後6周年目に向けて、一言ずつ、もらえればと、思います。
and looking ahead to the 6th year, I'd like each of you to say a few words.
じゃあ、喋りたい人。
So, who wants to start?
健康で！
With good health!
楽しく！
Having fun!
有意義に！
Meaningfully!
会社のルールを守って！
Following the company rules!
怒られないように！
So we don't get scolded!
せーの！
One, two...!
オファンタジー！
O-fantasy!
何も決まってないけど…
Nothing's really decided yet, but...
ファンタジー！イエーイ！
Fantasy! Yay!
これからも、3期生をよろしくお願いします！
Please continue to support the 3rd generation!
まだまだライブは続くので、お楽しみに！
The live isn't over yet, so please look forward to it!
ヘーイ！ヘーイ！
Hey! Hey!
打上花火
作詞・作曲 米津玄師
Uchiage Hanabi
Lyrics & Composition: Kenshi Yonezu
あの日見渡した渚を
I still remember the shore I looked out upon that day
今も思い出すんだ
and I still remember it now
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
Words carved in the sand
君の後ろ姿
and the sight of your back
寄り返す波が 足元をよぎり
The returning waves wash over my feet
何かを攫う
and sweep something away
夕凪の中 日暮れだけが
In the evening calm, only the sunset
通り過ぎて行く
passes by
パッと光って咲いた
It suddenly lit up and bloomed
花火を見ていた
We watched the fireworks
きっとまだ
Surely, still...
終わらない夏が
a summer that hasn't ended yet
曖昧な心を
Our ambiguous hearts
解かして繋いだ
were melted and connected
この夜が
This night...
続いて欲しかった
I wanted it to go on forever
あと何度君と同じ花火を見られるかなって
I wonder how many more times I can see the same fireworks with you.
笑う顔に何ができるだろうか
I wonder what I can do for your smiling face.
傷つくこと 喜ぶこと 繰り返す波と情動
Hurting, rejoicing, repeating waves and emotions.
焦燥 最終列車の音
Impatience, the sound of the last train.
何度でも言葉にして君を呼ぶよ
I'll call you as many times as it takes.
波を選び もう一度
Choosing a wave, once more.
もう二度と悲しまずに済むように
So that we don't have to be sad ever again.
ハッと息をのめば 消えちゃいそうな光が
When I catch my breath, the light seems like it's about to disappear.
きっとまだ胸に住んでいた
Surely it still lived in my heart.
手を伸ばせば触れた あったかい未来は
The warm future that I could touch if I reached out...
ひそかに二人を見ていた
...was secretly watching the two of us.
パッと花火が 夜に咲いた 夜に咲いて
Suddenly, the fireworks bloomed in the night, blooming in the night.
静かに消えた 離さないで もう少しだけ
Silently vanished. Don't let go, just a little longer.
もう少しだけ このままで
Just a little longer, just as we are.
あの日見渡した渚を 今も思い出すんだ
I still remember the beach I looked out over that day.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉 君の後ろ姿
The words carved in the sand, your back as you walked away.
パッと光って咲いた 花火を見ていた
I was watching the fireworks that suddenly lit up and bloomed.
きっとまだ終わらない夏が
Surely the summer is not over yet.
曖昧な心を 解かして繋いだ
Melting and connecting our ambiguous hearts...
この夜が続いて欲しかった
...I wanted this night to go on.
La la la...
新宝島 作詞・作曲：山口一郎
Shin Takarajima Lyrics/Composition: Ichiro Yamaguchi
次と その次と
The next, and the one after that,
その次と線を引く 続けた
and the one after that, drawing lines, I continued.
次の目的地を
The next destination,
目的地を描くんだ
I'm painting the destination.
宝島
Treasure Island.
このまま君を連れて行くよ
I'll take you away just like this.
丁寧 丁寧 丁寧に描くと
Carefully, carefully, if I paint it carefully...
揺れたり 震えたりした線で
...with lines that swayed and trembled...
丁寧 丁寧 丁寧に描くと
...carefully, carefully, if I paint it carefully...
決めていたよ
...I had decided.
次も
Next time
その次も
And the next
And the next after that
まだ目的地じゃない
It's not the destination yet
夢の
Of dreams
景色を
The scenery
探すんだ宝島
We'll search for Treasure Island
あー！
Ah!
このまま君を連れて行くよ
I'll take you with me just like this
丁寧に丁寧に歌うと
If I sing carefully, carefully...
揺れたり震えたりしたって
Even if it sways or trembles...
丁寧に丁寧に歌うと決めてたけど
I'd decided to sing carefully, carefully, but...
このまま君を連れて行くよ
I'll take you with me just like this
丁寧に丁寧に描くよ
I'll draw it carefully, carefully
揺れたり震えたりしたって
Even if it sways or trembles...
丁寧に丁寧に歌うよ
I'll sing carefully, carefully
それでも君を連れて行くよ
Even so, I'll take you with me
揺れたり震えたりしたって
Even if it sways or trembles...
描くよ君の歌を
I'll draw your song
Square of Magic!